Guide to the Central Washington University Athletics Department, Team Sports Collection 1923-2007 (bulk 1965-1995)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Video Cassettes of Sporting Events, IX
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Montana State University (Football), September 9, 1995 (Box-item 47-32)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon State College (Football), September 17, 1995 (Box-item 47-33)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), September 30, 1995 (Box-item 47-34)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 7, 1995 (Box-item 47-35)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 7, 1995 (Box-item 47-36)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Southern Oregon State College (Football), October 28, 1995 (Box-item 47-37)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Southern Oregon State College (Football), October 28, 1995 (Box-item 47-38)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon State College (Football), November 4, 1995 (Box-item 47-39)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon State College (Football), November 11, 1995 (Box-item 47-40)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon State College (Football), November 11, 1995 (Box-item 47-41)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Football), November 18, 1995 (Box-item 47-42)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Mary (N.D.) (Football), December 9, 1995 (Box-item 47-43)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Findley College (Ohio) (Football), December 16, 1995 (Box-item 47-44)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Mary (N.D.) (Football), December 9, 1995 (Box-item 48-1)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Findley College (Ohio) (Football), December 16, 1995 (Box-item 48-2)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Findley College (Ohio) (Football), December 16, 1995 (Box-item 48-3)
  - Videos – Senior Interviews (Football), 1995 (Box-item 48-4)
  - Videos – Highlights Tape (Football), 1995 (Box-item 48-5)
  - Videos – Highlights Tape (Football), 1995 (Box-item 48-6)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Whitworth College (Football), September 14, 1996 (Box-item 48-7)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), October 5, 1996 (Box-item 48-8)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Pacific Lutheran University (Football), October 5, 1996 (Box-item 48-9)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 12, 1996 (Box-item 48-10)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound (Football), October 12, 1996 (Box-item 48-11)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon State College (Football), November 9, 1996 (Box-item 48-12)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. I.S.U. (Box-item 48-13)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. I.S.U. (Box-item 48-14)
  - Videos – Senior Highlights (Football) (Box-item 48-15)
  - Videos – Senior Highlights (Football) (Box-item 48-16)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Montana State University – Billings (Women’s Basketball), November 30, 2000 (Box-item 48-17)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. St. Martin’s University (Women’s Basketball), December 8, 2001 (Box-item 48-18)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of California at San Diego (Women’s Basketball), December 29, 2001 (Box-item 48-19)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Anchorage (Women’s Basketball), January 12, 2002 (Box-item 48-20)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Humbolt State University (Women’s Basketball), January 17, 2002 (Box-item 48-21)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Northwest Nazarene University (Women’s Basketball), February 6, 2002 (Box-item 48-22)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Women’s Basketball), February 9, 2002 (Box-item 48-23)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Anchorage (Women’s Basketball), February 14, 2002 (Box-item 48-24)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon University (Women’s Basketball), February 21, 2002 (Box-item 48-25)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Yakima Valley Community College (Women’s Basketball), November 14, 2002 (Box-item 48-26)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Northwest University (Women’s Basketball), November 30, 2002 (Box-item 48-27)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon University (Women’s Basketball), December 5, 2002 (Box-item 48-28)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Humbolt State University (Women’s Basketball), December 7, 2002 (Box-item 48-29)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Lynn University (Women’s Basketball), December 17, 2002 (Box-item 48-30)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. St. Martin’s University (Women’s Basketball), January 9, 2003 (Box-item 48-31)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Northwest Nazarene University (Women’s Basketball), January 11, 2003 (Box-item 48-32)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Seattle Pacific University (Women’s Basketball), January 18, 2003 (Box-item 48-33)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Women’s Basketball), January 25, 2003 (Box-item 48-34)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Fairbanks (Women’s Basketball), January 30, 2003 (Box-item 48-35)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Anchorage (Women’s Basketball), February 1, 2003 (Box-item 48-36)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. St. Martin’s University (Women’s Basketball), February 8, 2003 (Box-item 48-37)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Seattle Pacific University (Women’s Basketball), February 15, 2003 (Box-item 48-38)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Seattle University (Women’s Basketball), February 22, 2003 (Box-item 48-39)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Fairbanks (Women’s Basketball), February 27, 2003 (Box-item 48-40)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Humbolt State University (Women’s Basketball), March 6, 2003 (Box-item 48-41)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon University (Women’s Basketball), March 8, 2003 (Box-item 48-42)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Montana State University at Billings (Women’s Basketball), March 14, 2003 (Box-item 48-43)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Central Washington University (Women’s Basketball), November 14, 2003 (Box-item 48-44)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western New Mexico University (Women’s Basketball), November 17, 2003 (Box-item 48-45)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Warner Pacific College (Women’s Basketball), November 28, 2003 (Box-item 49-1)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Northwest College (Women’s Basketball), November 29, 2003 (Box-item 49-2)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Seattle Pacific University (Women’s Basketball), December 4, 2003 (Box-item 49-3)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. [Evergreen State University] (Women’s Basketball), December 13, 2003 (Box-item 49-4)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of California at San Diego (Women’s Basketball), December 30, 2003 (Box-item 49-5)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Seattle University (Women’s Basketball), January 8, 2004 (Box-item 49-6)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Women’s Basketball), January 10, 2004 (Box-item 49-7)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Anchorage (Women’s Basketball), January 15, 2004 (Box-item 49-8)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Fairbanks (Women’s Basketball), January 17, 2004 (Box-item 49-9)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon University (Women’s Basketball), January 22, 2004 (Box-item 49-10)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Humbolt State University (Women’s Basketball), January 24, 2004 (Box-item 49-11)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. St. Martin’s University (Women’s Basketball), January 29, 2004 (Box-item 49-12)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Northwest Nazarene University (Women’s Basketball), January 31, 2004 (Box-item 49-13)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University (Women’s Basketball), February 5, 2004 (Box-item 49-14)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Fairbanks (Women’s Basketball), February 12, 2004 (Box-item 49-15)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Humbolt State University (Women’s Basketball), February 19, 2004 (Box-item 49-16)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon University (Women’s Basketball), February 21, 2004 (Box-item 49-17)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Seattle Pacific University (Women’s Basketball), March 6, 2004 (Box-item 49-18)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Warner Pacific College (Women’s Basketball), November 20, 2004 (Box-item 49-19)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Humbolt State University (Women’s Basketball), January 11, 2001 (Box-item 49-20)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Cascade College (Women’s Basketball), November 16, 2001 (Box-item 49-21)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Northwest College (Women’s Basketball), November 17, 2001 (Box-item 49-22)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Cascade College (Women’s Basketball), November 23, 2001 (Box-item 49-23)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Northwest Nazarene University (Women’s Basketball), November 24, 2001 (Box-item 49-24)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Seattle University (Women’s Basketball), January 5, 2002 (Box-item 49-25)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Whitman College (Women’s Basketball), November 22, 2002 (Box-item 49-26)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Lewis and Clark College (Women’s Basketball), November 23, 2002 (Box-item 49-27)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Seattle University (Women’s Basketball), January 23, 2003 (Box-item 49-28)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Seattle University (Women’s Basketball), February 22, 2003 (Box-item 49-29)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Anchorage (Women’s Basketball), March 1, 2003 (Box-item 49-30)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. Montana State University at Billings (Women’s Basketball), November 21, 2003 (Box-item 49-31)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of California at San Diego (Women’s Basketball), November 22, 2003 (Box-item 49-32)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. University of Alaska Fairbanks (Women’s Basketball) (Box-item 49-33)
  - Videos – Central Washington University vs. [Unidentified team] (Women’s Basketball) (Box-item 49-34)
- Oversized photographs, artifacts and ephemera, X
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1997 (Box-folder 50-1)
  - N.A.I.A. Certificates of Wrestling All-American Scholar Athletes, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 50-2)
  - Sporting Events Supplements to the Ellensburg Daily Record, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 50-3)
  - All-American Kodak Football Team Certificate, 1988 (Box-folder 50-4)
  - All-American Wrestling Team Certificates, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 50-5)
  - Football Team, Team photograph, 1989 (Box-folder 51-1)
  - Football Team, Team photograph, 1990 (Box-folder 51-2)
  - Football Team, Team photograph, 1991 (Box-folder 51-3)
  - Football Team, Team photograph, 1992 (Box-folder 51-4)
  - Football Team, Team photograph, 1998 (Box-folder 51-5)
  - Football Team, Team photograph (Box-folder 51-6)
  - Soccer team (Men), Team photograph, 1989 (Box-folder 51-7)
  - Soccer team (Women), Team photograph, 1991 (Box-folder 51-8)
  - N.A.I.A. Certificate to the Hall of Fame (Gary Frederick), 1997 (Box-folder 51-9)
  - N.A.I.A. Certificates, 1964-1975 (Box-folder 51-10)
  - Williamson’s 1948 Balanced Vote “Little” All-Americans (Box-folder 51-11)
  - First Annual Pear Bowl, 1946--Galley copies in color (Box-folder 51-12)
  - Letter jackets (Box 52)
  - Letter jackets (Box 53)
  - Letter jackets (Box 54)
  - Championship banners – N. A. I. A. Swimming and Diving National Champions, Women’s Division, 1986 (Box 55)
  - Championship banners – N. A. I. A. Wrestling National Champions, 1971 (Box 56)
  - Championship banners – N. A. I. A. Wrestling National Champions, 1974 (Box 57)
  - Championship banners – N. A. I. A., Division II, Football National Champions, 1995 (Box 58)
  - Championship banners - N. A. I. A. Swimming and Diving National Champions, Men’s Division, 1984 (Box 59)
  - Championship banners - N. A. I. A. Swimming and Diving National Champions, Men’s Division, 1986 (Box 60)
  - Championship banners - N. A. I. A. Swimming and Diving National Champions, Men’s Division, 1987 (Box 61)
  - Wildcat mascot costume head (Box 62)
- Scrapbooks, XI
  - Basketball, 1964-1965 (Box-item 63-1)
  - Basketball, 1965-1966 (Box-item 63-2)
  - Basketball, 1966-1967 (Box-item 63-3)
  - Basketball, 1967-1968 (Box-item 64-1)
  - Basketball, 1968-1969 (Box-item 64-2)
  - Basketball, 1969-1970 (Box-item 64-3)
  - Basketball, 1971-1972 (Box-item 65-1)
  - Basketball, 1972-1973 (Box-item 65-2)
  - Basketball, 1973-1974 (Box-item 65-3)
  - Basketball, 1974-1975 (Box-item 66-1)
  - Basketball, 1975-1976 (Box-item 66-2)
  - Basketball, 1988-1989 (Box-item 67-1)
  - Basketball, 1988-1989 (Box-item 67-2)
  - Basketball, 1989-1990 (Box-item 67-3)
  - Football/Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box-item 68-1)
  - Football, 1995 (Box-item 68-2)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1964-1979 (Box-item 69-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1981-1982 (Box-item 70-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1982-1983 (Box-item 71-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, January 1984-April 1985 (Box-item 72-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, May 1985-December 1985 (Box-item 73-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1985-1986 (Box-item 74-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1986-1987 (Box-item 75-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1987-1988 (Box-item 76-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1990-1991 (Box-item 77-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1991-1992 (Box-item 78-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1992-1993 (Box-item 78-2)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, Fall 1993 (Box-item 79-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, Winter/Spring 1993-1994 (Box-item 79-2)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1994-1995 (Box-item 79-3)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1995-1996 (Box-item 80-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1996-1997 (Box-item 80-2)
  - Miscellaneous clippings; Men’s Basketball, Spring 1996-1998 (Box-item 81-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings (Except Football/Basketball), 1997-1998 (Box-item 81-2)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1998-1999 (Box-item 82-1)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, 1999-2000 (Box-item 83-1)
  - Media Guides, Photos, Statistics, 1942-2008; Additon (Box-folder Series XII)
  - John Foster- media guides, 1942-1996; rg 30-7-13 (Box-folder 84-1)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1965 (Box-folder 85-1)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 85-2)
  - Evergreen Conference -Media Guides, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 85-3)
  - Football Media Guides, 1974 (Box-folder 85-4)
  - Evergreen Conference -Media Guides, 1970 (Box-folder 85-5)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1972 (Box-folder 85-6)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1975 (Box-folder 85-7)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1976 (Box-folder 85-8)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1977 (Box-folder 85-9)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 85-10)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1980 (Box-folder 85-11)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1981 (Box-folder 85-12)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1982 (Box-folder 85-13)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 85-14)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 85-15)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 86-1)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1987 (Box-folder 86-2)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 86-3)
  - Game Program- Media guides, 1989 (Box-folder 86-4)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 86-5)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 86-6)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1993 (Box-folder 86-7)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1995 (Box-folder 86-8)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1996 (Box-folder 86-9)
  - CWU Football Media Guides, 1998-2005 (Box-folder 86-10)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 87-1)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 87-2)
  - CWU Men's Basketball: Game guide, 1976 (Box-folder 87-3)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 87-4)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 87-5)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 87-6)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1982 (Box-folder 87-7)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 87-8)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1985 (Box-folder 87-9)
  - NAIA: Men's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 87-10)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 87-11)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 87-12)
  - CWU Men's Basketball: Game guide, 1999 (Box-folder 87-13)
  - CWU Women's Basketball, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 87-14)
  - CWU Track and Field Stats, 1980-1998 (Box-folder 88-1)
  - CWU Track and field guide, 1985 (Box-folder 88-2)
  - CWU Track and field guide, 1986 (Box-folder 88-3)
  - CWU Track and field guide, 1987 (Box-folder 88-4)
  - CWU Track and field program, 1991 (Box-folder 88-5)
  - CWU Track and field guide, 1992 (Box-folder 88-6)
  - CWU Track and field guide, 1993 (Box-folder 88-7)
  - CWU Track and field guide, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 88-8)
  - CWU Track and field regional Championships, 1995 (Box-folder 88-9)
  - CWU Track and Field Yearbook, 1996 (Box-folder 88-10)
  - GNAC Track and Field Championships, 2003 (Box-folder 88-11)
  - GNAC Track and Field Championships, 2004 (Box-folder 88-12)
  - GNAC Track and Field Championships, 2005 (Box-folder 88-13)
  - GNAC Track and Field Championships, 2009 (Box-folder 88-14)
  - CWU Spring Sports, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 88-15)
  - NAIA Football Stats, 1963-1998 (Box-folder 89-1)
  - NAIA All American Division. I-II Football, 1963-1998 (Box-folder 89-2)
  - NCAB NAIA Basketball Releases, 1964-1998 (Box-folder 89-3)
  - NAIA Baseball News release, 1965-1998 (Box-folder 89-4)
  - NAIA All-merican Basketball teams Division. I-II, 1967-1998 (Box-folder 89-5)
  - NAIA Track and Field, 1972-1997 (Box-folder 89-6)
  - Evergreen Conference All sports, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 89-7)
  - CWU Women's Basketball, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 90-1)
  - NAIA NW Nook, 1975 (Box-folder 90-2)
  - NAIA NW Nook, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 90-3)
  - NAIA NW nook, 1977 (Box-folder 90-4)
  - NAIA Newsletter- D1 Sports, 1978 (Box-folder 90-5)
  - NAIA Women's Soccer, Basketball, 1981-1998 (Box-folder 90-6)
  - NAIA D1 guide and Handbook, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 90-7)
  - NAIA volleyball, 1987-1997 (Box-folder 90-8)
  - NAIA Men's Soccer, 1987-1997 (Box-folder 90-9)
  - CWU Softball, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 90-10)
  - NAIA All am Swimming, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 90-11)
  - NAIA Men's Tennis, Wrestling, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 90-12)
  - CWU Women's Soccer, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 90-13)
  - CWU Football: All-time Scores, 1901-1998 (Box-folder 91-1)
  - CWU Football Stats, year by year games, 1904-1990 (Box-folder 91-2)
  - CWU Football Stats, all time conference standing, 1923-1995 (Box-folder 91-3)
  - Evergreen conference football stats roundup, 1949-1953 (Box-folder 91-4)
  - Evergreen conference football scores, 1957 (Box-folder 91-5)
  - Football Career Totals, 1958-1998 (Box-folder 91-6)
  - Evergreen conference footballl stats summary, 1960 (Box-folder 91-7)
  - Evergreen conference footballl stats summary, 1961 (Box-folder 91-8)
  - Football Stats, all conference team, 1964 (Box-folder 91-9)
  - Evergreen conference footballl stats summary, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 91-10)
  - Evergreen conference footballl stats summary, 1966 (Box-folder 91-11)
  - Evergreen conference football press release, 1967 (Box-folder 91-12)
  - Evergreen conference footballl stats summary, 1968 (Box-folder 91-13)
  - CWU Football teams, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 91-14)
  - CWU Football awards, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 91-15)
  - CWU football wrap-up, 1975 (Box-folder 91-16)
  - CWU Football, 1976 (Box-folder 91-17)
  - CWU football wrap-up, 1976 (Box-folder 91-18)
  - CWU football wrap-up, 1977 (Box-folder 91-19)
  - CWU football wrap-up, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 91-20)
  - Evergreen conference coaches, 1978 (Box-folder 91-21)
  - CWU football wrap-up, 1978 (Box-folder 91-22)
  - CWU football wrap-up, 1979 (Box-folder 91-23)
  - Evergreen confernce football stats, 1980 (Box-folder 91-24)
  - CWU Football stats, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 91-25)
  - Evergreen conference football stats, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 91-26)
  - CWU Football box scores, 1980-1999 (Box-folder 91-27)
  - Columbia, Mt. Ranier, Mt. Hood Teams and Information, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 92-1)
  - Evergreen conference football stats, 1981 (Box-folder 92-2)
  - Evergreen confernce football stats, 1982 (Box-folder 92-3)
  - Evergreen conference football-all-stars, >1983 (Box-folder 92-4)
  - Football stats, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 92-5)
  - Columbia football stats, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 92-6)
  - Evergreen conference new release, 1984 (Box-folder 92-7)
  - CWU Football stats, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 92-8)
  - CWU Football stats, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 92-9)
  - CFA Rosters, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 92-10)
  - CWU Football stats, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 92-11)
  - CWU Football stats, 1995 (Box-folder 92-12)
  - CWU Football stats, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 92-13)
  - CWU Football stats, 1997 (Box-folder 92-14)
  - Football CFA Stats, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 92-15)
  - CWU Football Stats, 1998 (Box-folder 92-16)
  - CWU Football stats, 1999 (Box-folder 92-17)
  - CWU Football stats, 1999 (Box-folder 92-18)
  - CWU Football stats, 1999 (Box-folder 92-19)
  - CWU Athletics Press releases, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 92-20)
  - CWU Football, 2000 (Box-folder 92-21)
  - CWU Football stats, 2000 (Box-folder 93-1)
  - CWU game by game Football stats, 2004 (Box-folder 93-2)
  - CWU Football stats, 2005 (Box-folder 93-3)
  - CWU Football stats, 2006 (Box-folder 93-4)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, All-time coaches, 1901-2002 (Box-folder 94-1)
  - CWU Men's basketball History, 1922-1988 (Box-folder 94-2)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Stats, 1907-1946 (Box-folder 94-3)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Totals, 1952-1999 (Box-folder 94-4)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1962-1990 (Box-folder 94-5)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Stats, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 94-6)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Stats, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 94-7)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Stats, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 94-8)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Stats, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 94-9)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Stats, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 94-10)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Stats, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 94-11)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Stats, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 94-12)
  - CWU Men's Basketball Stats, 2001 (Box-folder 94-13)
  - CWU Basketball Box score Stats, 2002 (Box-folder 94-14)
  - CWU Women's Basketball Stats, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 95-1)
  - CWU Women's Basketball -Year by year stats, 1974-1998 (Box-folder 95-2)
  - CWU Women's Basketball-Career Totals, 1977-2000 (Box-folder 95-3)
  - CWU Women'sbasketball hoop camp, 1978 (Box-folder 95-4)
  - CWU Women's Basketball stats, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 95-5)